A Guide to the Records of the Office of the Dean of Virginia Tech Carilion School of Medicine, Cynda Ann Johnson, 2008-2018
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series I: Subject Files
  - Macy Faculty Scholars Program (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Macy Foundation (Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - School of Medicine - Malpractice (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - MLK Day of Service, 2017-01-16 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - MLK Day of Service (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - School of Medicine - Master's Degree Programs (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - MBAs for Physicians throughout VT (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Master of Public Health (MPH) Update (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - School of Medicine - Master of Public Health (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Match Day #1, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Match Day #2, 2014-03-21 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Match Day 2, 2015-03-20 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Match Day 1 (Private), 2015-03-20 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Match Day, 2017-03-17 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Match Day 1A, 2017-03-17 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Match Day 1B, 2017-03-17 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Chris McLaughlin, 2015-01-20 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - McNamee, Mark (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Medicaid Funding (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Medical Education and State Authorization Reciprocity Agreement (SARA) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Military (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Millenials (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Molecular Genetics (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Monographs (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Memorandum of Understanding (MOUs) (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - MOU - Mungeli, India (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - MOU - Virginia Tech (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Mike Moyer, Assoc. VP Development VT (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - MS Dinner of Champions, 2015-09-22 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - MS Dinner of Champions, 2016-09-27 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - MS Dinner of Champions, 2018-09-11 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Multiple Mini Interviews (MMI) (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Murphy, Edward G. (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Jane L. Murray, MD, Visiting Professor, 2011-07-28-2011-07-29 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Narrative Medicine (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - NAACP (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - National Board of Medical Examinations (NBME) Scores (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - National Campaign Steeting Committee, 2008-09-12 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Nationals Council for SARA (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - National Kidney Foundation (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - National Resident Matching Program (NRMP) Carilion, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - NRMP, 2016 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - New Developing Medical Schools (AAMC), 2008-07-09-2008-07-12 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - New Medical Schools (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Newsletters, 2014-2016 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Dr. Lois Nora (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Obesity (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - OB/GYN, Department of (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Opole/Wroclaw, 2017-09-14-2017-09-21 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Opole, Poland Visit, 2010-06-09 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Oral Health (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Org. Charts (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Orientation - Class of 2019, 2015-07-27 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Orientation - Class of 2020, 2016-07-25 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Orientation - Class of 2021, 2017-07-24 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Orientation, 2018 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - OSCE (Objective Structured Clinical Examination) Development, 2009-09-08 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Osteopathic (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Osteopathic Graduates (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Pain Management (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Palliative Care (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Patient - Centered Medical Home (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Patient Experience (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Patient Safety (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Performance Evaluations (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Perry, Helen (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Philanthropy (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Physician Annual Review (Carilion) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Physician Bonus Compensation Guidelines (Carilion) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Physician Leave Options (Carilion) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Physician Professional Staff (Carilion) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Physician Wellness (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Physician Workforce (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Pingleton, Susan (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Pinn, Melvin (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Pinn, Tanika (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - School of Medicine - Plagiarism (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Poetry Contests (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Poland Trip (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Policies (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Polycom (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Public-Private Education Act (PPEA) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Practice Based PhD (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Pre-Med Advisors (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Preventive Medicine Residency (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - PriceWaterhouseCoopers (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Primary Care (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Professionalism Committee (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Psychiatry, Department of (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Psychiatry Faculty Meeting, 2014-07-31 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - VT Public Health Program - Final CEPH (Council on Education for Public Health) Self-Study, 2012-09-10 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - VT Public Health Program - Meeting of Advisory Board Materials, 2011-11-30 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - VT Public Health Program - Meeting of Advisory Board Materials, 2013-03-25 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Richard Alan Kaslow Curriculum Vitae, 2014-07 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Quality (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Quality and Safety Curriculum Mtg., 2016-02-22 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Quality and Safety Curriculum (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Radford University (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Recovery Act Funding (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Recovery Act Limited Competition (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Requistions (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Research (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Research Acceleration Program (RAP) Grants (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Research Certificates (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Research Insitute (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Student Research, 2015-03-10 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Research Value Domain (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Residency Schedules (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Roanoke Articles (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - President Maxey Roanoke College (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Roanoke College (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Roanoke College - Alpha Epsilon Delta (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Roanoke College - Public Health Studies Advisory Board (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Roanoke Orthapaedic Center (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Roanoke Regional Airport (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Roanoke Regional Parternship (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Roanoke Hope Valley (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation (RWJF) County-by-County Health Rankings (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Rural Medicine (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Russia (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Safety Curriculum (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Salem Virginia Medical Center (VAMC) (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Dr. Timothy Sands (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - President Sands Installation Event, 2014-10-17 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Scholarships, 2015-11 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Carilion Clinic Scholarship for Athletics Recipients, 2016-2017 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Scholarships, 2018-04 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - School of Health Professions (JCHS, RU, VT) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - School of Medicine (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - School of Medicine - Dental Curriculum (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - School of Medicine - Frequently Asked Questions (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - School of Medicine - Medical Student Assessment (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - School of Medicine - Patient Centered Learning (PCL) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - School of Medicine - Peer Review (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - School of Medicine - Pharmaceuticals (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - School of Medicine - Salary Benchmarks (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - School of Medicine - Scholarships (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - School of Medicine - Student Affairs (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - School of Medicine - Student Analysis (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - VTC School of Medicine - Student Distinction (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - School of Medicine - Students (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Science Festival (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Senate Bill #581 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Senate Finance Committee, 2012-08-26 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Society of General Internal Medicine (SGIM) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Shadowing Guidelines (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Simulation (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Skochelak, Susan (American Medical Association) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Smith, Margaret L. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Dr. Sidney Smith (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Society of Teachers of Family Medicine (STFM) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Glenda Snyder (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Sonosite (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Guest Speakers (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Sophie Davis College (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - State Authorization and Medical Education (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Step One Outline (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Strategic Planning (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Student Clinician Ceremony, 2014-07-02 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Student Clinician Ceremony, 2015-07-01 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Student Research (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Student Research Letter (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Substance Abuse Mental Health Services Administration (SAMHSA) Mtg., 2016-06-29 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - SAMHSA, 2017-12-19 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - SAMHSA Mtg. Charlottesville, 2017-01-09 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Succession Planning (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Surgery, Department of (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Surveys - VTCSOM (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Surveys (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Engagement Survey, 2016 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Symposium: Girls to STEM-MD, 2017-05-16 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Taiwan (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Tajikistan (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Taubman Museum of Art (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Poster Presentation - Teaching and Practicing QI in a Generalist Continuity Clinic, 2010-11 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - TEDMED (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Telemedicine Services (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Tenure and Promotion (VT) (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Title IV Administration, Washington DC, 2012-09-10-2012-09-14 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Tobacco Commission Funds (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Tuition Assistance Grant (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Translational Medicine Research Certificate (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Transgender Health Clinic (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Transition to Residency, 2016 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Uganda Contacts (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Uganda (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Ultrasound (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - School of Medicine - CURE (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - University of Iowa Dept. of Family Med 40th Anniversary Reunion, 2011-06-17-2011-06-18 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - University of Virginia (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - University of Virginia Mulholland Clerkship Report (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - University of Virginia School of Medicine (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Uranium Mining (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - United States Medical Licensing Examination (USMLE) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - USMLE - Dr. Dan Gebremedhin, 2011-10-02-2011-10-03 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Ut Prosim, 2008-05-02-2008-05-04 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Ut Prosim Society, 2010-04-23-2010-04-24 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Ut Prosim Society, 2009-04-24-2009-04-26 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Academy of Family Physicians (VAFP) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - VAFP, 2016-04-23 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Association of Collegiate Registrars and Admissions Officers (VACRAO), 2011-12-11-2011-12-13 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Bio Events (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Bio (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Virginia College of Osteopathic Medicine (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - VCU School of Medicine (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Department of Education, 2009-05-08 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Intercollegiate Anatomy Lab (VIAL) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - VA Medical Center (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - VA Medical School Affiliations (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - VA Network Annual State Conference, 2017-06-02 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Tech Academic Affairs Council, 2011-10-13 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - VT Advancement Division Presentation, 2016-12-14 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - VT Alumni Chapter Officers Forum, 2012-09-02 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - VT Alumni Meeting, Baltimore MD, 2012-06-14 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - VT Alumni East Tenn. Chapter, Kingsport TN, 2013-03-11 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - VT Alumni Assoc. North Carolina Triad Chapter, 2011-05-19 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - VT Alumni Assoc. (Roanoke/Franklin County), 2010-04-29 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - VT Board of Visitors (BOV) Academic Affairs Comm., 2010-05-22 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Virginia Tech BOV Guests, 2010-08-30 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Virginia Tech BOV, 2011-03-27 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Virginia Tech BOV Meeting, 2016-08-28 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - VTC Academic Health Center (AHC) Steering Committee (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Virginia Bio Life Sciences, 2008-10-09 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Virginia Tech (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Chairs with Dean Meeting, 2009-02-11 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Chairs with Dean Meeting, 2009-06-03 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - VTC Development Luncheon, 2010-05-12 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - VTC Economic Development Work Group (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Excellence in VA Government Award, 2015-11-13 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - VTC Expansion Project - Accreditation Timeline (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - VTC Faculty Assembly, 2009-02-02 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - VTC Faculty Orientation, 2010-05-19 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - VTC Faculty Orientation, 2010-05-13 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - VTC Faculty Orientation, 2010-07-13 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - VTC Faculty Orientation, 2010-08-13 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - VTC Faculty Orientation, 2011-06-15 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - VTC Grand Opening Celebration, 2011-05-07 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Impact on Economic Development, 2008-09-15 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - VT Integration, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - VTCSOM Integration, 2016 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - VTC Integration - Proposal, 2016-08 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Integration (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Integration Budget (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Integration Working Groups (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Integration - VT/VTCSOM (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - VTC Integration Final Docs (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - VTC Interprofessionalism Kick-Off, 2010-08-23 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Carilion Leadership Forum, 2010-05-11 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - VTC Master Plan (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - VTC Media Day, 2010-07-15 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - VT/VTCSOM MPH Capstone Seminar, 2012-04-12 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Carilion Partnership Mtg., 2017-06-02 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - VTC Partnership Meetings (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - School of Medicine Retreat, 2008-01-25 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - VTC Planning Retreat, 2010-03-31 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - VTC Research Institute (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Tech Carilion Research Institute (VTCRI) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - VTCRI Advisory Committee, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - VTCRI Steering Committee, 2017-09 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - VTCRI - Friedlander, Michael (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - VTC Strategic Plan (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - VTC Unfinished (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - #VTC Unfinished, 2017-01-17 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - University of Alabama at Birmingham (UAB), 2018-01-05 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - VA State Science and Engineering Fair Planning Committee (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - VTC Women in Medicine, 2010-07-22 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - VTC Staff Meeting, 2011-02-11 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - VTC Women in Medicine, 2011-05-24 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - VTC Women in Medicine, 2011-09-12 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - VTC Women in Medicine, 2011-06-21 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - VTC Working Group (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - VTCSOM Groundbreaking, 2008-10-06 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Charter Class (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - School of Medicine - Class of 2014 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - School of Medicine - Class of 2015 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Class of 2019 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Class Officers (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - VTCSOM Class Size Increase (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - VTCSOM - Faculty Assembly, 2014-03-17 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - VTCSOM Faculty Orientation, 2010-02-25 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - VTCSOM Faculty Orientation, 2010-05-14 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - VTCSOM Finance Working Group (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - VTCSOM Leadership Meeting, 2010-03-31 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - VTCSOM Leadership Meeting, 2009-12-14 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - VTCSOM Library (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - VT/VTCSOM MPH Advisory Board (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - VTCSOM Retreat, 2010-01-15 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - VTCSOM Retreat, 2011-03-11-2011-03-12 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Staff Meetings VTCSOM (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - VTCSOM Update - VT BOV, 2016-06-05 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - VTCSOM Women Faculty Event, 2010-05-10 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - VTCSOM Women Faculty Event, 2010-06-21 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - VTCSOM and Research Institute, 2008-10-09 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - VTCSOM&RI Carilion Clinic/VT Partnership Meeting (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - VT College of Agriculture and Life Sciences (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - VT College of Agriculture and Urban Studies (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - VT College of Engineering (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - VT College of Natural Resources (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - VT College of Science, 2008-04-05 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - VT College of Veterinary Medicine (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - VT Leadership Visit, 2018-04-19 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - VT Deans' Forum Global Engagement, Blacksburg VA, 2014-03-25-2014-03-27 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Virginia Tech Deans' Summer Retreat, 2010-07-15-2010-07-16 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - VT Deans' Planning Retreat, 2010-11-11 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - VT Deans' Retreat, Folder 1 of 2, 2011-01-28-2011-01-30 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - VT Deans' Retreat, Folder 2 of 2, 2011-01-28-2011-01-30 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - VT Council of Deans (COD) Retreat, Alexandria VA, 2014-03-06-2014-03-08 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - VT Deans' Retreat, 2015-02-19-2015-02-21 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - VT Deans' Retreat, Annapolis MD, 2017-02-24-2017-02-26 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - VT Deans' Visit to Institute for Advanced Learning and Research (IALR) and Southern VA Higher Education Center (SVHEC), 2011-04-26 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - VT Dept Heads Council, 2010-03-16 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - VTCSOM Faculty Orientation, 2010-03-16 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Economic Vitality - VT Strategic Plan Review (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - VT Faculty Senate Presentation, 2016-10-04 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - VT - Foundation - Info (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising Event - Dean Johnson Host, 2012-09-03 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - VT Joint Meeting COD, American Conference of Academic Deans (ACAD) VPs, Assoc. Provosts, 2010-12-07 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - VT Gerontology Graduate Certificate Celebration, 2010-04-15 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - VT Health Services Division Presentation, 2011-02-28 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Kids' Tech University, 2011-04-09 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - VT Legacy Society Event, 2008-09-05 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Let's Talk Public Health Youth Conference, VT, 2012-08-01 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Let's Talk Public Health Youth Conference, VT, 2013-07-26 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - VT Medicine and Society Program, 2010-02-18 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - VT Old Guard Reunion, Blacksburg, 2013-05-23 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - VT Outreach Council, 2010-05-25 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - VT - President's Inclusive Exec. Council Meetings (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - University Promotion and Tenure (VT) (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - VT Provost - Thanassis Rikakis (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - VT Regional Campaign Kick-Off, 2009-03-19 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - VT Regional Campaign Kick-Off, 2008-10-29-2008-10-30 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - VT Regional Campaign Kick-Off, 2008-11-20 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Richmond Campaign Kick-Off, 2009-09-29-2009-09-30 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - VT/Serge, 2011-08-19 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - VT - Serge Meeting, 2013-08-15 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - VT University Development, 2011-09-12 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - VT University Strategic Plan (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - VT University Strategic Plan, 2012-2018 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - VT Student Recognition Ceremony, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - VT - Ut Prosim, 2017-04-01 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - VT Women Council, 2008-03-20 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Virginia Tobacco and Health Research Repository, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Virginia Tobacco and Health Research Repository - Official Documents (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Virginia Tobacco and Health Research Repository, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Virginia Western Community College (VWCC) (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Vision for the Future Commission - Application (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Visiting Student Application Services (VSAS) (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Tracey Vosburgh - VT University Relations (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Wake Forest University School of Medicine (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Wake Forest, 2009-10-05 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Wake Forest CTSA Application (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Wake Forest University (WFU)/ Translational Science Institute (TSI)/ Carilion Partnership (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Barbara Walsh (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Barbara Walsh (VTC Expansion Project) (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Barbara Walsh Mtg., 2017-03-07 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Warranties (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Weather Announcements (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Whatley/Bishop Meetings (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - What's in Your White Coat, 2016-08-31 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - What's in Your White Coat, 2017 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - White Coat, 2018 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - School of Medicine - White Coat Ceremonies (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - White Coat Essays, 2015-10-23 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - White Coat Essays - Class of 2021, 2017 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Women in Leadership and Philanthropy (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Women in STEM (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Wonju College of Medicine, 2010-10-05 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Wonju Delegation, 2011-05-20 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Wonju College of Medicine (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Wonju (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Wonju Materials (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Wonju Korea, 2009-10-06-2009-10-13 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Wonju, Korea (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Wonju, South Korea, 2015 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Substantive Change Prospectus for the SACS Commission on Colleges, 2009-07 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - SACS, 2009-12-04 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - SACS/Title IV (Murphy, Johnson, Workman), 2009-12-11 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - SACS, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - SACS Annual Meeting, 2010-12-04-2010-12-07 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - SACS Meeting, 2011-02-14 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - SACS Annual Meeting, 2011-12-03-2011-12-06 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - SACS Meeting Materials, 2011-02-14 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - State Council on Higher Education in Virginia (SCHEV) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - SACS Candidacy, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Southern Associations of Colleges and Schools Commission on Colleges (SACSCOC) Site Visit, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - SACS - Brian McAulay Visit, 2013-08-29 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - SACSCOC Resource Manual (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - SACSCOC Visit, 2013-09-30-2013-10-02 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - SACS (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - SACSCOC Principles of Accreditation (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - SACSCOC Accreditation Materials (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - SCHEV/SACS (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - SCHEV (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - School of Medicine SCHEV Visit, 2008-05-05 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - SCHEV, 2008-05-12 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - VTC Potential Pathways to Regional Accreditation Draft (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - SCHEV, 2011-06-23 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - SACSCOC, 2016-07-22 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - SACSCOC Meeting, Atlanta, 2016-07-22 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - SACSCOC, 2016-09-16 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Letter to SCHEV (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - SACSCOC (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - SACSCOC Binder (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Title IV Binder (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Confidential Medical and Scientific Advisory Council (MSAC) (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - VTCSOM (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2008-01-16 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2008-01-30 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2008-02-13 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2008-02-27 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2008-03-12 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2008-03-26 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2008-04-09 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2008-05-07 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2008-06-18 (Box 16, Folder 9)